const  movieEmojis = [
  {
    "question": "🌳🌲🎲🦒🦓🐘👦👧👨",
    "answer": "Jumanji",
    "hint": "A board game that comes to life with wild adventures."
  },
  {
    "question": "💼👩☂️🎶",
    "answer": "Mary Poppins",
    "hint": "A magicl nanny who brings joy to a London Family."
  },
  {
    "question": "🚘🚗🚙",
    "answer": "Cars",
    "hint": "Animated vehicles with unique personalities."
  },
  {
    "question": "👧📚👀🥾🎂🏫",
    "answer": "Matilda",
    "hint": "A young girl with telekinetic powers takes on her parents and a headmistress."
  },
  {
    "question": "😴👧",
    "answer": "Sleeping Beauty",
    "hint": "A classic Disney princess cursed to eternal slumber."
  },
  {
    "question": "🦁👑",
    "answer": "The Lion King",
    "hint": "The coming-of-age story of a young lion who becomes king."
  },
  {
    "question": "🐜🐜🐜",
    "answer": "Antz",
    "hint": "An animated film featuring an ant named Z in a colony."
  },
  {
    "question": "👻🐷🐷🧙👧👦",
    "answer": "Spirited Away",
    "hint": "A young girl's journey through a mysterious, magical world."
  },
  {
    "question": "👑👰",
    "answer": "Princess Bride",
    "hint": "A classic fairy tale adventure filled with love, comedy, and swashbuckling."
  },
  {
    "question": "🌳🌳🐻📖👦🏿🐅",
    "answer": "The Jungle Book",
    "hint": "Mowgli's adventures with animal friends in the jungle."
  },
  {
    "question": "🐓🏃 ♂️",
    "answer": "Chicken Run",
    "hint": "A group of chickens trying to escape from a farm."
  },
  {
    "question": "❄️☃️👧🏼👧🏼",
    "answer": "Frozen",
    "hint": "Two royal sisters and a kingdom trapped in eternal winter."
  },
  {
    "question": "🐘🎪",
    "answer": "Dumbo",
    "hint": "A flying elephant who overcomes adversity."
  },
  {
    "question": "🔎🐠",
    "answer": "Finding Nemo",
    "hint": "A clownfish's journey to find his lost son."
  },
  {
    "question": "🐀🥘🧑 🍳",
    "answer": "Ratatouille",
    "hint": "A rat with a talent for cooking in Paris."
  },
  {
    "question": "👧🏻📚🌹👹",
    "answer": "Beauty and the Beast",
    "hint": "A tale of love and acceptance in an enchanted castle."
  },
  {
    "question": "👳🏽 ♂️🐒🧞 ♂️⛵️👸🏻",
    "answer": "Aladdin",
    "hint": "A young man's adventures with a magic lamp and a genie."
  },
  {
    "question": "🧙🧙 ♀️🐀👦",
    "answer": "The Witches",
    "hint": "A young boy's encounter with a coven of witches."
  },
  {
    "question": "🤠🧸🪀📖⚡️",
    "answer": "Toy Story",
    "hint": "Toys that come to life when humans aren't around."
  },
  {
    "question": "👸🏻🐸",
    "answer": "The Princess and the Frog",
    "hint": "A modern twist on a classic fairy tale set in New Orleans."
  },
  {
    "question": "🎩👱 ♂️🍫🏭",
    "answer": "Willy Wonka & the Chocolate Factory",
    "hint": "A visit to a magical chocolate factory."
  },
  {
    "question": "👶🦌🌲",
    "answer": "Bambi",
    "hint": "A young deer's journey through the forest."
  },
  {
    "question": "🎶🌊👧🏻",
    "answer": "Song old the Sea",
    "hint": "A magical tale set in Ireland about a selkie and her brother."
  },
  {
    "question": "👧🏻🌸🌊🌋⛵️",
    "answer": "Moana",
    "hint": "A daring journey across the ocean to save her people."
  },
  {
    "question": "🌌👽",
    "answer": "E.T.",
    "hint": "A young boy befriends an extraterrestrial stranded on Earth."
  },
  {
    "question": "🤥👦🪓",
    "answer": "Pinocchio",
    "hint": "A wooden puppet's quest to become a real boy."
  },
  {
    "question": "👴🏻🎈🎈🎈🏠⬆️",
    "answer": "Up",
    "hint": "An elderly man's adventure in a flying house."
  },
  {
    "question": "👯 ♀️👨 👩 👧 👧🪤",
    "answer": "The Parent Trap",
    "hint": "Twin sisters who meet for the first time at summer camp."
  },
  {
    "question": "👹🐉🗡️👩🏻",
    "answer": "Mulan",
    "hint": "A young woman disguises herself as a man to save China."
  },
  {
    "question": "🔊🎶💃🏞️",
    "answer": "The Sound of Music",
    "hint": "A musical journey with a governess and a singing family in Austria."
  },
];